Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files P-T, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files A
  - Subject Files R
    - Rawls, Betty (Box A-99, Folder 62)
      Note on folder: "(Deceased)."
    - Rawls, Lou (Box A-99, Folder 63)
      Also two press releases and one velox print.
      Photographer if identified: Harry Langdon, Bruno of Hollywood, Playboy
    - Rawls, Lou (Box A-99, Folder 64)
      Also two velox prints, one press release, and one press kit in folder.
      Photographer if identified: Harry Langdon, Peterkin
    - Rawls, Lou Jr. (Box A-99, Folder 65)
    - Rawls, William (Box A-99, Folder 66)
    - Ray, Barbara (Box A-99, Folder 67)
    - Ray, Brenda (Box A-99, Folder 68)
    - Ray, Carline (Box A-99, Folder 69)
    - Ray, Doris T. (Box A-99, Folder 70)
    - Ray, Elizabeth (Box A-99, Folder 71)
    - Ray, Gene A. (Box A-99, Folder 72)
    - Ray, Glenn (Box A-99, Folder 73)
    - Ray, Goodman + Brown (Box A-99, Folder 74)
    - Ray, Henry H. Jr. (Box A-99, Folder 75)
    - Ray, James (Ptl.) (Box A-99, Folder 76)
      Photographer if identified: Photographic Unit NYC Transit Authority
    - Ray, James E. (Box A-99, Folder 77)
    - Ray, Joe (Box A-99, Folder 78)
    - Ray, Katherine (Box A-99, Folder 79)
      Photographer if identified: Monclova Photographers
    - Ray, Lativia (Box A-99, Folder 80)
    - Ray, Louis (Box A-99, Folder 81)
      Prints have résumés on verso.
    - Ray, Marguerite (Box A-99, Folder 82)
    - Ray, Martha (Box A-99, Folder 83)
    - Ray, Ola (Box A-99, Folder 84)
    - Ray, Ron (Box A-99, Folder 85)
    - Ray, Rosa M. (Box A-99, Folder 86)
    - Ray, Ruby (Miss) (Box A-99, Folder 87)
    - Ray, Sandra E. (Box A-99, Folder 88)
    - Ray, Sheila (Box A-99, Folder 89)
    - Ray, Sugar (Box A-99, Folder 90)
    - Ray, Sugar L. (Box A-99, Folder 91)
    - Ray, Ursula (Box A-99, Folder 92)
    - Ray, Victoria (Mrs.) (Box A-99, Folder 93)
    - Ray, Von (Box A-99, Folder 94)
      Photographer if identified: Ken Howard
    - Ray, Walter I. Jr. (Box A-99, Folder 95)
    - Ray, William (Box A-99, Folder 96)
    - Rayburn, Chris (Box A-99, Folder 97)
    - Ray-Dars, The (Box A-99, Folder 98)
    - Raydio (Box A-99, Folder 99)
    - Raye, Jimmy (Box A-99, Folder 100)
      Photographer if identified: Michigan State University
    - Rayford, Carol Yvonne (Box A-99, Folder 101)
      Note on folder: "(See Mrs. Ada Jones)."
    - Raymond, Ana (Box A-99, Folder 102)
    - Raymond, Ann (Box A-99, Folder 103)
    - Raymond, Bro. 17X (Box A-99, Folder 104)
    - Raymond, Eugene A. (Box A-99, Folder 105)
      Photographer if identified: Jack T. Franklin
    - Raymond, Harriet (Miss) (Box A-99, Folder 106)
    - Raymond, James (Box A-99, Folder 107)
    - Raymond, Spanish (Box A-99, Folder 108)
      Subject's full name is "Raymond Marquez." Also contains one velox print.
    - Raynor, Essex (Box A-99, Folder 109)
    - Rays of the Stars (Box A-99, Folder 110)
    - Rayson, Jim (Box A-99, Folder 111)
    - Razaf, Andy (Box A-99, Folder 112)
    - Razor, Reynolds (Box A-99, Folder 113)
    - Read, James "Chom" (Box A-99, Folder 114)
    - Readen, Thomas (Box A-99, Folder 115)
    - Reading, Silvera (Box A-99, Folder 116)
    - Reagan, John W. (Box A-99, Folder 117)
    - Reagan, Nancy (Box A-99, Folder 118)
      Photographer if identified: Juanita M. Cole
    - Reagon, Bernice (Box A-99, Folder 119)
    - Reagon, Bernice (Box A-99, Folder 120)
    - Realidades (Box A-99, Folder 121)
    - Reality (Box A-99, Folder 122)
    - Reason, Joseph P. (Box A-99, Folder 123)
      Photographer if identified: Greg Harris
    - Reasoner, Harry (Box A-99, Folder 124)
      Note on folder: "(See Cardinal Custing)."
    - Reaves, Olen (Box A-99, Folder 125)
    - Reaves, Robert (Box A-99, Folder 126)
    - Reaves, Susie (Box A-99, Folder 127)
    - Reaves, Edward P. Jr. (Box A-99, Folder 128)
    - Rebb, James (Box A-99, Folder 129)
    - Rechbund, Mildred (Box A-99, Folder 130)
    - Rechter, Gwenn (Box A-99, Folder 131)
    - Reckling, Frances Kraft (Box A-99, Folder 132)
      Also two strips of negatives (three images) and one paper stereotype matrix.
    - Reckling, Howard O. (Box A-99, Folder 133)
    - Reckling, Richard Kraft (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-99, Folder 134)
    - Reckord, Lloyd (Box A-99, Folder 135)
    - Record, Eugene (Box A-99, Folder 136)
    - Records (Music) (Box A-99, Folder 137)
      Also ten newspaper & magazine clippings.
    - Rector, Charles (Box A-99, Folder 138)
    - Rector, Eddie (Box A-99, Folder 139)
    - Rector, Shirley (Box A-99, Folder 140)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Ed Bagwell (News Voice International) James Gilbert
    - Red Cross (Box A-99, Folder 141)
      Note on folder: "see: American Red Cross Workers, etc."
      Photographer if identified: Parkway Studios
    - Red Cross (Harlem) (Box A-99, Folder 142)
      Prints stuck together and stuck to folder.
    - Red, F. Arthur (Box A-99, Folder 143)
    - Red Hook (Artists rendering of) (Box A-99, Folder 144)
    - Red Hook Park (Box A-99, Folder 145)
    - Red Sea (Box A-99, Folder 146)
      One photocopied map.
    - Red, White and Maddox (Box A-99, Folder 147)
    - Redd, Dolores (Box A-99, Folder 148)
    - Redd, Gene (Box A-99, Folder 149)
    - Redd, Harry (Box A-99, Folder 150)
    - Redd, M. Paul (Box A-99, Folder 151)
    - Redd, Mamie (Box A-99, Folder 152)
    - Redd, Orial (Box A-99, Folder 153)
      Photographer if identified: Anthony Vitulli
    - Redd, Paul (Box A-99, Folder 154)
    - Redd, Paula (Box A-99, Folder 155)
    - Redd, Sharon (Box A-99, Folder 156)
    - Redd, Veronica (Box A-99, Folder 157)
    - Redd, Vi (Box A-99, Folder 158)
    - Reddick, Alan W. (Box A-99, Folder 159)
    - Reddick, Eunice (Box A-99, Folder 160)
      Photographer if identified: New York University
    - Reddick, John T. (Box A-99, Folder 161)
    - Reddick, L. D. (Dr.) (Box A-99, Folder 162)
      Also two negatives, one paper stereotype matrix, and one press release.
      Photographer if identified: Dummett, A. Hansen, Rapid News Photos
    - Reddick, Leroy (Box A-99, Folder 163)
      Photographer if identified: International News Photo
    - Reddick, Louise (Box A-99, Folder 164)
    - Reddick, Willie (Box A-99, Folder 165)
    - Redding, Curtis (Box A-99, Folder 166)
      Note on folder: "St. Johns."
    - Redding, George (Lt.) (Box A-99, Folder 167)
      Photographer if identified: Dummett, Photokraft, Chick Solomon, International News Photos, Edward Graham
    - Redding, J. Saunders (Box A-99, Folder 168)
    - Redding, Jacob L. (Dr.) (Box A-99, Folder 169)
      One paper stereotype matrix.
    - Redding, James O. (Sgt.) (Box A-99, Folder 170)
    - Redding, Louis L. (Box A-99, Folder 171)
    - Reddings, The (Box A-99, Folder 172)
    - Redds + the Boys (Box A-99, Folder 173)
    - Redeemer Methodist Church (Box A-99, Folder 174)
    - Redfield, Amy (Rev.) (Box A-99, Folder 175)
    - Redford, Hattie (Mrs.) (Box A-99, Folder 176)
    - Redford, Robert (Box A-99, Folder 177)
      One promotional flier.
    - Redford, Sheila (Box A-99, Folder 178)
    - Redgrave, Lynn (Box A-99, Folder 179)
    - Redhead, Buster (Box A-99, Folder 180)
    - Redhead, Chester (Dr.) (Box A-99, Folder 181)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Al Burley, Tex Harris, Cecil Layne, Curt Clemons, Al Levine
    - Redhead, Chester Jr. (Box A-99, Folder 182)
    - Redhead, Francis (Sir) (Box A-99, Folder 183)
    - Redhead, Gladys (Box A-99, Folder 184)
    - Redistricting (Box A-99, Folder 185)
    - Redlich, Norman (Box A-99, Folder 186)
      Photographer if identified: Board of Ed. City of New York
    - Redman, Dewey (Box A-99, Folder 187)
    - Redman, Don (Box A-99, Folder 188)
    - Redmond, Gregory (Box A-99, Folder 189)
    - Redmond, Hertacine (Miss) (Box A-99, Folder 190)
    - Redpath, Virginia (Box A-99, Folder 191)
      Photographer if identified: Pan Am P.R.
    - Redwine, Preston (Mrs.) (Box A-99, Folder 192)
      Photographer if identified: Lorenzo Tucker
    - Redwood, Bessie (Box A-99, Folder 193)
    - Redwood, Les (Box A-99, Folder 194)
    - Reeb, James (Box A-99, Folder 195)
    - Reeberg, Lucien (Box A-99, Folder 196)
    - Reeberg, Patricia A. (Box A-99, Folder 197)
    - Reece, Charles (Box A-99, Folder 198)
    - Reece, Claude Sr. (Mrs.) (Box A-99, Folder 199)
    - Reece, Cornell H. (Box A-99, Folder 200)
    - Reece, Debra (Box A-99, Folder 201)
    - Reece, Geneva (Mrs.) (Box A-99, Folder 202)
    - Reece, Glen (Box A-99, Folder 203)
      Photographer if identified: Office of News Services University of Washington
    - Reece, Mari (Box A-99, Folder 204)
    - Reed, Alaina (Box A-99, Folder 205)
      Also two velox prints and one press release.
      Photographer if identified: Roy Blakey
    - Reed, Alaina (Box A-99, Folder 206)
    - Reed, Albert E. (Dr. + Mrs.) (Box A-99, Folder 207)
    - Reed, Arthur (Box A-99, Folder 208)
      Photographer if identified: Dave Greene, Cecil Layne, Harris Photo
    - Reed, Barry (Box A-99, Folder 209)
    - Reed, Billy (Box A-99, Folder 210)
    - Reed, Calvin C. Sr. (Box A-99, Folder 211)
    - Reed, Claude Jr. (Box A-99, Folder 212)
      Photographer if identified: Hakim
    - Reed, Dana K. (Box A-99, Folder 213)
    - Reed, Dorothy (Box A-99, Folder 214)
    - Reed, Eugene T. (Dr.) (Box A-99, Folder 215)
      Photographer if identified: Impact Photo, Wide World Photos, George Frye
    - Reed, F. Arthur (Rev.) (Box A-99, Folder 216)
    - Reed, Floyd H. (Box A-99, Folder 217)
      Photographer if identified: George Jervas
    - Reed, Fred T. (Box A-99, Folder 218)
    - Reed, Glenda (Box A-99, Folder 219)
    - Reed, Grant (Box A-99, Folder 220)
    - Reed, Gregory J. (Box A-99, Folder 221)
    - Reed, Harriet (Box A-99, Folder 222)
      Photographer if identified: Lufthansa Archive
    - Reed, Herb (Box A-99, Folder 223)
    - Reed, Irene (Box A-99, Folder 224)
    - Reed, Ishmael (Box A-99, Folder 225)
    - Reed, James (Box A-99, Folder 226)
    - Reed, James (Mrs.) (Box A-99, Folder 227)
    - Reed, Jason (Box A-99, Folder 228)
    - Reed, Jerry (Box A-99, Folder 229)
      Photographer if identified: Llewellyn Ransom Press Photo Service
    - Reed, Jessica A. (Box A-99, Folder 230)
    - Reed, Jimmy (Box A-99, Folder 231)
    - Reed, John L. (Box A-99, Folder 232)
    - Reed, Joseph (Mrs.) (Box A-99, Folder 233)
    - Reed, Jozella (Box A-99, Folder 234)
    - Reed, Kenneth V. (Box A-99, Folder 235)
    - Reed, Laura (Box A-99, Folder 236)
    - Reed, Laverne (Box A-99, Folder 237)
    - Reed, LeGrand (Box A-99, Folder 238)
    - Reed, Loragene (Box A-99, Folder 239)
      On sheet of paper in folder is written "See American Airlines (Loragene Reed, Hostess)."
    - Reed, Louis J. (Box A-99, Folder 240)
    - Reed, Luther (Box A-99, Folder 241)
    - Reed, Margaret (Box A-99, Folder 242)
      Photographer if identified: Bunny Studio
    - Reed, Matt (Box A-99, Folder 243)
    - Reed, Michelle (Box A-99, Folder 244)
    - Reed, Myra (Box A-99, Folder 245)
    - Reed, Rosemary (Box A-99, Folder 246)
    - Reed, Sam (Box A-99, Folder 247)
    - Reed, Sandra (Box A-99, Folder 248)
    - Reed, Sidney (Box A-99, Folder 249)
    - Reed, Smith (Box A-99, Folder 250)
    - Reed, Talullah (Box A-99, Folder 251)
    - Reed, Tracy (Box A-99, Folder 252)
    - Reed, Vera (Box A-99, Folder 253)
    - Reed, Vincent E. (Dr.) (Box A-99, Folder 254)
    - Reed, Vivian (Box A-99, Folder 255)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, James J. Kriegsmann
    - Reed, Wilbert (Box A-99, Folder 256)
    - Reed, Wiley (Box A-99, Folder 257)
    - Reed, William (Box A-99, Folder 258)
    - Reed, Willis (Box A-99, Folder 259)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Hairston Photo News Service, Russell F. Ley, Camera Associates, United Press International
    - Reeder, James T. (Rev.) (Box A-99, Folder 260)
    - Reel, Brenard (Box A-99, Folder 261)
    - Reel, Lonnie (Box A-99, Folder 262)
    - Reerens, Clauddie J. (Box A-99, Folder 263)
      Note on folder: "(See Elijah Weatherby)."
    - Rees, Evan (Box A-99, Folder 264)
      One photocopy of a photograph.
    - Rees, Mina (Dr.) (Box A-99, Folder 265)
    - Reese, Arthur (Box A-99, Folder 266)
    - Reese, Claude (Box A-99, Folder 267)
    - Reese, Della (Box A-99, Folder 268)
      Photographer if identified: [Al]ex Summer, TWA
    - Reese, Della Jr. (Box A-99, Folder 269)
    - Reese, Diane Yolanda (Box A-99, Folder 270)
    - Reese, Joe (Mr. + Mrs.) (Box A-99, Folder 271)
    - Reese, Joseph (Box A-99, Folder 272)
      Photographer if identified: Dan Miller
    - Foxx, Red (Box A-99, Folder 273)
    - Reese, John (Box A-100, Folder 1)
    - Reese, Mamie B. (Box A-100, Folder 2)
      Photographer if identified: Burley Photo Services, Federal Aviation Agency
    - Reese, Otis (Box A-100, Folder 3)
    - Reese, Percival Hugo (Box A-100, Folder 4)
    - Reese, Robert (Box A-100, Folder 5)
    - Reese, Roxanne (Box A-100, Folder 6)
    - Reese, Sandi (Box A-100, Folder 7)
    - Reese, Theodore (Box A-100, Folder 8)
    - Reese, Theodore S. and Reese, Steve (Box A-100, Folder 9)
    - Reeter, Rose (Box A-100, Folder 10)
    - Reeve, Irene (Box A-100, Folder 11)
    - Reeves-Bey, Carolyn (Box A-100, Folder 12)
    - Reeves, Donald St. George (Box A-100, Folder 13)
    - Reeves, Frank D. (Dr.) (Box A-100, Folder 14)
    - Reeves, Garth (Box A-100, Folder 15)
    - Reeves, Godfrey (Dr. and Mrs.) (Box A-100, Folder 16)
    - Reeves, Irving (Box A-100, Folder 17)
    - Reeves, Jean (Box A-100, Folder 18)
    - Reeves, Jerome (Lt.) (Box A-100, Folder 19)
    - Reeves, Leonard (Box A-100, Folder 20)
    - Reeves, Martha (Box A-100, Folder 21)
    - Reeves, Martha (and The Vandellas) (Box A-100, Folder 22)
    - Reeves, Richard (Box A-100, Folder 23)
    - Reeves, Richard D. (Box A-100, Folder 24)
    - Refuge Temple (Box A-100, Folder 25)
    - Regal Shoe Store (Box A-100, Folder 26)
    - Regan, Helene (Box A-100, Folder 27)
    - Regan, James F. (Box A-100, Folder 28)
    - Regan, Ned (Box A-100, Folder 29)
    - Regan, Robert T. (Chief) (Box A-100, Folder 30)
    - Regents Scholarship Winners (1963) (Box A-100, Folder 31)
    - Regent Theatre (Box A-100, Folder 32)
    - "Reggae" (Box A-100, Folder 33)
    - Regional Conference Committee (Box A-100, Folder 34)
      Photographer if identified: Poindexter
    - Registration (Box A-100, Folder 35)
    - Reid, Anne C. (Dr.) (Box A-100, Folder 36)
    - Reid, Arthur (Box A-100, Folder 37)
    - Reid, Carole (Box A-100, Folder 38)
    - Reid, Charles H. (Box A-100, Folder 39)
    - Reid, "Chum" (Box A-100, Folder 40)
    - Reid, Dr. Clarence Martin (Box A-100, Folder 41)
    - Reid, Clyde (Box A-100, Folder 42)
    - Reid, Curtis A. (Box A-100, Folder 43)
    - Reid, Daisy (Mrs.) (Box A-100, Folder 44)
    - Reid, David (Box A-100, Folder 45)
    - Reid, Eddie (Box A-100, Folder 46)
    - Reid, Eddie (Box A-100, Folder 47)
    - Reid, Edith (Dr.) (Box A-100, Folder 48)
    - Reid, Edward (Box A-100, Folder 49)
      Photographer if identified: Blue Bird Photo Studios
    - Reid, Eilen H. (Box A-100, Folder 50)
    - Reid, Etta (Box A-100, Folder 51)
    - Reid, Everett (Box A-100, Folder 52)
    - Reid, F.M. (Bishop) (See Clayborn, J.H.) (Box A-100, Folder 53)
    - Reid, F. Theodore (Dr.) (Box A-100, Folder 54)
    - Reid, Frank M. (Bishop) (Box A-100, Folder 55)
    - Reid, Frank Madison (Box A-100, Folder 56)
    - Reid, Fred (Box A-100, Folder 57)
    - Reid, George (Box A-100, Folder 58)
    - Reid, Gloria (Box A-100, Folder 59)
    - Reid, Gwendolyn (Box A-100, Folder 60)
    - Reid, Herman (Box A-100, Folder 61)
    - Reid, Inez (Mrs.) (Box A-100, Folder 62)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Francis C. WardInc.
    - Reid, Irene (Box A-100, Folder 63)
      One photocopied print with Irene Reid's ms. autograph and inscription on the image.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Monroe S. Frederick II
    - Reid, James E. (Box A-100, Folder 64)
      Photographer if identified: American Cancer Society
    - Reid, Joseph A. (Box A-100, Folder 65)
    - Reid, Leone (Box A-100, Folder 66)
    - Reid, Lorraine (Miss) (Box A-100, Folder 67)
    - Reid, Mary P. (Mrs.) (Box A-100, Folder 68)
    - Reid, Maurice A. (Box A-100, Folder 69)
    - Reid, Mildred (Box A-100, Folder 70)
    - Reid, Ogden (Box A-100, Folder 71)
    - Reid, Tim (Box A-100, Folder 72)
      Also one promotional 35mm color slide in acidic sleeve. Slide has been separated from print. Image recto discolored by sleeve.
    - Reid, P.A. (Dr.) (Box A-100, Folder 73)
    - Reid, Pam (Box A-100, Folder 74)
    - Reid, Pearl (Rev.) (Box A-100, Folder 75)
      Photographer if identified: Carl Nesfield
    - Reid, Raymond (Box A-100, Folder 76)
      Photographer if identified: Columbia University
    - Reid, Robert (Mayor) (Box A-100, Folder 77)
    - Reid, Walter (Box A-100, Folder 78)
    - Reid, Trevor A. (Box A-100, Folder 79)
    - Reid, Wendell (Mr. and Mrs.) (Betty Granger) (Box A-100, Folder 80)
    - Reid, William Ferguson (Box A-100, Folder 81)
    - Reid, William (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-100, Folder 82)
    - Reid, Whitelaw (Box A-100, Folder 83)
      One print mounted to heavy board.
      Photographer if identified: Herald Tribune/Rice
    - Reid, Whitelaw (Mrs.) (Box A-100, Folder 84)
    - Reid, William (Box A-100, Folder 85)
    - Reid, William (Box A-100, Folder 86)
      Photographer if identified: New York City Housing Authority, Jersey Pictures Inc.
    - Reid, William A. (Box A-100, Folder 87)
    - Reid, Willie Mae (Box A-100, Folder 88)
    - Reifer, Rosetta (Box A-100, Folder 89)
      One print cut-out and affixed to heavy board. Board has separated from print.
      Photographer if identified: W. Smith, International News Photos, Dummett
    - Reifer, Walter (Box A-100, Folder 90)
      One print has newspaper clipping affixed to verso with tape.
      Photographer if identified: James C. Campbell, William C. Wilson
    - Reilly, Hazel (Box A-100, Folder 91)
      Photographer if identified: Andrew Richards
    - Reilly, John F. (Box A-100, Folder 92)
      Photographer if identified: Art Green
    - Reilly, Thomas A. (Dep. Chief) (Box A-100, Folder 93)
      Print is discolored and giving off a chemical odor. Tape affixed to verso has badly yellowed.
    - Reine, Peter M. (Box A-100, Folder 94)
    - Reinford, Alvin (Box A-100, Folder 95)
    - Reinhardt, John (Dr. (Box A-100, Folder 96)
    - Reisman, Leonard E. (Mr.) (Box A-100, Folder 97)
      Photographer if identified: Arthur Avedon
    - Reissen-Weber, John (Box A-100, Folder 98)
    - Reitor, Alexander III (Box A-100, Folder 99)
    - Reives, Mary S. (Box A-100, Folder 100)
    - Religion (Box A-100, Folder 101)
    - Relsey, George (Box A-100, Folder 102)
    - Remer, Victor (Box A-100, Folder 103)
      Photographer if identified: The Children's Aid Society
    - Remick, Lee (Box A-100, Folder 104)
    - Remler, Emily (Box A-100, Folder 105)
    - Rempson, Joe (Dr.) (Box A-100, Folder 106)
      One black and white Polaroid print.
      Photographer if identified: Bronx Community College
    - Renae, Shawn (Box A-100, Folder 107)
    - Renaissance Casino (Box A-100, Folder 108)
    - Render, Eva S. (Box A-100, Folder 109)
    - Render, Frank II (Box A-100, Folder 110)
    - Render, Mattline (Box A-100, Folder 111)
    - Rene, Hodelin F., Jr. (Box A-100, Folder 112)
    - Renee, La Marr (Box A-100, Folder 113)
    - Renegades On Board (Box A-100, Folder 114)
      Photographer if identified: L. Boykin
    - Renie, Michael (Box A-100, Folder 115)
    - Renny, Chris (See Vivian Bennette) (Box A-100, Folder 116)
    - Renny Basketball Team (Box A-100, Folder 117)
    - Renoir, Jean (Box A-100, Folder 118)
    - Renolds, Grant (Box A-100, Folder 119)
    - Rent Strike (Box A-100, Folder 120)
    - Rentas "Beef" (Box A-100, Folder 121)
    - Reos, Mary Lou (Box A-100, Folder 122)
      Photographer if identified: Irene Baker
    - Repelyea, Horace "Blue" (Box A-100, Folder 123)
      Photographer if identified: New York Racing Association
    - "Repertoire Workshop" (Box A-100, Folder 124)
    - Rephael, Eden (Box A-100, Folder 125)
    - Reppetto, Thomas (Box A-100, Folder 126)
    - Reptiles (Box A-100, Folder 127)
    - Republic of New Africa (Box A-100, Folder 128)
    - Republicans (Box A-100, Folder 129)
      Also five single-leaf photocopied typescript captions.
    - Republicans (Women) (Box A-100, Folder 130)
    - Rashad, Phylicia (Box A-100, Folder 131)
      Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Curt Clemons
    - Reshard, Leroy (Box A-100, Folder 132)
    - Resident Advisory Council (Box A-100, Folder 133)
      Most prints with typescript captions attached with paperclips.
    - Resin, Pearl O. (Box A-100, Folder 134)
    - Resnick, Joe (Box A-100, Folder 135)
    - Ressley, Calvin (Rev.) (Box A-100, Folder 136)
    - Restaurants and Clubs (Box A-100, Folder 137)
      Photographer if identified: Norman Frederick, Dave Greene, Bro. David McAdams, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, James Gilbert, Harris Photo, James Gilbert/News Voice International, Dave Barnett
    - Restaurants and Clubs (Box A-100, Folder 138)
    - Resto, Luis (Box A-100, Folder 139)
      Photographer if identified: Glenn Edwards
    - Restoration Building (Box A-100, Folder 140)
    - Resurrection City (Box A-100, Folder 141)
    - Retirement (Box A-100, Folder 142)
    - Reuben, Charles (Box A-100, Folder 143)
    - Reuben, Odell R. (Box A-100, Folder 144)
    - Reuman, William (Box A-100, Folder 145)
      Photographer if identified: Frederick H. Simmons
    - Reuther, Walter (Box A-100, Folder 146)
    - Revell, Ruth (Box A-100, Folder 147)
      Photographer if identified: Ernest Agnew
    - Revels, John (Box A-100, Folder 148)
    - Revis, Marva (Box A-100, Folder 149)
      Photographer if identified: George M. West, Cecil Layne, Bert Miles
    - Revitalization Corps. (Box A-100, Folder 150)
    - Rey, Andrew W. (Box A-100, Folder 151)
    - Rey, Louis (Box A-100, Folder 152)
    - Reyes, Elna (Box A-100, Folder 153)
    - Reyes, Jose (Box A-100, Folder 154)
    - Reyes, Judith (Box A-100, Folder 155)
    - Reyes, Roberto (Box A-100, Folder 156)
    - Reynolds, Allie (Box A-100, Folder 157)
      Photographer if identified: The F & M Schaeffer Brewing Co.
    - Reynolds, Anthony (Box A-100, Folder 158)
    - Reynolds, Ann (Box A-100, Folder 159)
      Photographer if identified: André Beckles
    - Reynolds, Barbara A. (Box A-100, Folder 160)
    - Reynolds Singers, Art (Box A-100, Folder 161)
    - Reynolds, Burt (Box A-100, Folder 162)
    - Reynolds, C.R. (Box A-100, Folder 163)
      Also one three-leaf typescript release, attached with paperclip.
    - Reynolds, Charles (Box A-100, Folder 164)
    - Reynolds, Collins (Box A-100, Folder 165)
      Also one newspaper clipping an envelope.
    - Reynolds, Ellen (Box A-100, Folder 166)
    - Reynolds, Elsie (Box A-100, Folder 167)
    - Reynolds, Eugene (Box A-100, Folder 168)
    - Reynolds, Everett (Box A-100, Folder 169)
    - Reynolds, Everett E. (Box A-100, Folder 170)
    - Reynolds, Frederick (Box A-100, Folder 171)
      Also one three-leaf typescript release.
    - Reynolds, Grant (Box A-100, Folder 172)
      Also one paper stereotype matrix. Also one single-leaf flier advertising the sesquicentennial of the African Methodist Episcopal Zion Church (1946). One print has badly-yellowed adhesive on the recto and verso.
      Photographer if identified: International News Photo, Rapid News Photo, Cecil Layne, A. Hansen, Dummett, W. Smith, James C. Campbell, Harris Photo
    - Reynolds, Grant (Box A-100, Folder 173)
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, Rapid News Photo, Nichols, Photokraft, Mae Kyles
    - Reynolds, Grant (Mrs.) (Box A-100, Folder 174)